[
  {
    "Question": "What are the minimum number of primary indexes that can be created in SAP?",
    "opt1": "1",
    "opt2": "2",
    "opt3": "3",
    "opt4": "None of the above",
    "correctAns": "1",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the maximum number of base tables that can be used in the project view in SAP?",
    "opt1": "1",
    "opt2": "2",
    "opt3": "3",
    "opt4": "4",
    "correctAns": "4",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the MAXIMUM number of secondary indexes that can be created?",
    "opt1": "1",
    "opt2": "2",
    "opt3": "3",
    "opt4": "None of the above",
    "correctAns": "None of the above",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a table is locked in exclusive mode, another user requests for read",
    "opt1": "Lock will be granted",
    "opt2": "Lock will not be granted",
    "opt3": "Lock will be generated in display mode",
    "opt4": "None of the above",
    "correctAns": "Lock will not be granted",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following best describes the data class application while creating a DDIC Table?",
    "opt1": "Master data - data that is rarely changed",
    "opt2": "Transaction data - data that is changed",
    "opt3": "Organization data - customizing data changed only rarely",
    "opt4": "None of the above",
    "correctAns": "Master data - data that is rarely changed",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "When would you store a table as a row-based select all option that apply:",
    "opt1": "When the number of records is huge",
    "opt2": "When all columns of the tables are relevant",
    "opt3": "When the table contains several repeated values",
    "opt4": "When aggregation is not required",
    "correctAns": "When aggregation is not required",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many append structures can be inserted in a table?",
    "opt1": "1",
    "opt2": "2",
    "opt3": "3",
    "opt4": "Any number of tables",
    "correctAns": "Any number of tables",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the maximum number of structures that can be included in table or structure?",
    "opt1": "9",
    "opt2": "8",
    "opt3": "4",
    "opt4": "7",
    "correctAns": "9",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the maximum number of tables joins that can be used in Hana?",
    "opt1": "100",
    "opt2": "150",
    "opt3": "50",
    "opt4": "25",
    "correctAns": "100",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "“MANDT” field in table makes it",
    "opt1": "Database dependent",
    "opt2": "Client independent",
    "opt3": "Client dependent",
    "opt4": "Database independent",
    "correctAns": "Client dependent",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "You are writing a transaction to update a database table. Which of the following elements must the program continue?",
    "opt1": "A logical database",
    "opt2": "A table buffers refresh on the application server",
    "opt3": "A call for enqueue dequeue function module",
    "opt4": "An authority check statement",
    "correctAns": [
      "A logical database",
      "A call for enqueue dequeue function module",
      "An authority check statement"
    ],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the difference between inner join and left outer joins?",
    "opt1": "Inner join - common entries",
    "opt2": "Left outer join - all entries from left side DB table and corresponding entries in other side",
    "opt3": "Inner join - all entries from both tables",
    "opt4": "Left outer join - only matching entries from the left side",
    "correctAns": [
      "Inner join - common entries",
      "Left outer join - all entries from left side DB table and corresponding entries in other side"
    ],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "When would you use a column store table instead of a row store table? Select option",
    "opt1": "When you require aggregation and analysis of values",
    "opt2": "When there are mainly distinct values in the table",
    "opt3": "When you want to enable a full-text search of the table",
    "opt4": "When the table has a small number of records",
    "correctAns": [
      "When you require aggregation and analysis of values",
      "When there are mainly distinct values in the table"
    ],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the maximum number of fields that can be part of a key field?",
    "opt1": "6",
    "opt2": "9",
    "opt3": "16",
    "opt4": "19",
    "correctAns": "16",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are applicable for table buffering?",
    "opt1": "The system loads all the records of the table into the buffer when one record is accessed.",
    "opt2": "When a record of the table is accessed, all the records having this relevant field are loaded into the buffer.",
    "opt3": "Only the records of a table that are really accessed are loaded.",
    "opt4": "All of the above",
    "correctAns": ["All of the above"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which table is used to store the control records for IDOC?",
    "opt1": "EDIDD",
    "opt2": "EDIDC",
    "opt3": "EDIDL",
    "opt4": "EDIDS",
    "correctAns": "EDIDC",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which of the following situations could a row store table be more suitable than a column store table?",
    "opt1": "The table contains data that you want to aggregate.",
    "opt2": "The table contains only a small number of records.",
    "opt3": "The table contains mainly distinct values per column across rows.",
    "opt4": "The table contains text that you want to search.",
    "correctAns": [
      "The table contains only a small number of records.",
      "The table contains text that you want to search."
    ],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Based on Primary and Secondary key, SAP automatically creates a primary index to improve performance for transparent tables.",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "correctAns": "True",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following can be achieved using Technical Settings?",
    "opt1": "Optimize storage space requirements",
    "opt2": "Table access behavior",
    "opt3": "Buffering required",
    "opt4": "All of the above",
    "correctAns": "All of the above",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are valid join types?",
    "opt1": "Self Join",
    "opt2": "Inner Join",
    "opt3": "Outer Join",
    "opt4": "All of the above",
    "correctAns": "All of the above",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are ways in which Standard Tables can be enhanced? (OR) Which can you use to enhance SAP standard tables and structures with fields?",
    "opt1": "Custom include",
    "opt2": "Direct field addition",
    "opt3": "Append structure",
    "opt4": "None of the options are correct",
    "correctAns": ["Custom include", "Append structure"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which table is the status stored, when an IDOC is created?",
    "opt1": "EDIDD (DATA RECORDS)",
    "opt2": "EDIDC (control records)",
    "opt3": "EDIDS (status records)",
    "opt4": "EDIDE",
    "correctAns": "EDIDS (status records)",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are access strategies for tables?",
    "opt1": "Index unique scan",
    "opt2": "Concatenation",
    "opt3": "Sort table scan",
    "opt4": "Full table scan",
    "correctAns": ["Index unique scan", "Concatenation", "Sort table scan"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do you add fields to an SAP-delivered transparent table without modification?",
    "opt1": "Use the database utility to enhance the definition on the database directly.",
    "opt2": "Add the new fields to the table definition.",
    "opt3": "Create an append structure containing the new fields.",
    "opt4": "Define a structure containing the new fields and include it in the table definition.",
    "correctAns": "Create an append structure containing the new fields.",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "When does SAP recommend that you use a full buffering type for a database table?",
    "opt1": "When the table is very large and frequently written",
    "opt2": "When the table is very small and frequently written",
    "opt3": "When the table is very large and seldom written",
    "opt4": "When the table is very small and seldom written",
    "correctAns": "When the table is very small and seldom written",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following customer modification options are available in the table maintenance generator?",
    "opt1": "Maintenance screens",
    "opt2": "Events",
    "opt3": "Search helps",
    "opt4": "Append searches",
    "correctAns": [
      "Maintenance screens",
      "Events",
      "Search helps",
      "Append searches"
    ],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "You want to add a field of type CURR to a transparent table. What else must you do?",
    "opt1": "Create a new field CUKY as a predefined type",
    "opt2": "Add a key field of type CUKY",
    "opt3": "Create a reference to a field of type CUKY",
    "opt4": "Add a check table that contains a field of type CUKY",
    "correctAns": "Create a new field CUKY as a predefined type",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which database table type is there a one-to-one relationship between the Dictionary table definition and the relevant physical table in the database?",
    "opt1": "Cluster table",
    "opt2": "Pooled table",
    "opt3": "Transparent table",
    "opt4": "Internal table",
    "correctAns": "Transparent table",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "You want to create a transparent table. Which of the following must you define to activate the table?",
    "opt1": "A delivery class",
    "opt2": "A foreign key",
    "opt3": "The primary key",
    "opt4": "The MANDT field",
    "opt5": "A short description",
    "correctAns": [
      "A delivery class",
      "The primary key",
      "The MANDT field",
      "A short description"
    ],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "You want to define a formal parameter to a subroutine that accepts only internal tables of types standard and type sorted as actual parameters. Which of the following generic ABAP data types must you use?",
    "opt1": "Sorted table",
    "opt2": "Standard table",
    "opt3": "Index table",
    "opt4": "Hashed table",
    "correctAns": ["Standard table", "Sorted table"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "In the technical settings for a transparent table, buffering is switched on and single record buffering is selected. Which statement uses the buffered data assuming that the WHERE clause contains restrictions for all key fields?",
    "opt1": "SELECT ENDSELECT.",
    "opt2": "SELECT SINGLE.",
    "opt3": "SELECT … INTO TABLE.",
    "opt4": "SELECT SINGLE FOR UPDATE.",
    "correctAns": "SELECT SINGLE.",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following transaction can you use to define transparent tables?",
    "opt1": "SE16N",
    "opt2": "SE38",
    "opt3": "SE11",
    "opt4": "SM37",
    "correctAns": "SE11",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following can you define in the technical settings of transparent table?",
    "opt1": "Size category",
    "opt2": "Table name",
    "opt3": "Data class",
    "opt4": "Buffering type",
    "opt5": "Delivery class",
    "correctAns": [
      "Size category",
      "Data class",
      "Buffering type",
      "Delivery class"
    ],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the SAP recommended naming convention for append structures of standard SAP tables?",
    "opt1": "The name of the append structure must start with Z OR Y.",
    "opt2": "The components of an append structure should start with ZZ or YY.",
    "opt3": "The components of an append structure should start with Z or Y.",
    "opt4": "The name of the append structure must start with ZZ or YY.",
    "correctAns": "The name of the append structure must start with Z OR Y.",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is required to fully specify a Table Type in the ABAP Dictionary?",
    "opt1": "Access type",
    "opt2": "Table key",
    "opt3": "Table size",
    "opt4": "Line type",
    "opt5": "Header line",
    "correctAns": ["Access type", "Table key", "Line type"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can we create transaction code for table maintenance?",
    "opt1": "Yes",
    "opt2": "No",
    "correctAns": "Yes",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Without maintaining the following, Table cannot be activated.",
    "opt1": "Entry help/check",
    "opt2": "Technical settings",
    "opt3": "Primary key",
    "correctAns": ["Technical settings", "Primary key"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Text table should consist of.",
    "opt1": "All the key fields of main table",
    "opt2": "All the fields of main table",
    "opt3": "SPRAS field for language key",
    "correctAns": "SPRAS field for language key",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can we include customizing include or append structure with pooled / cluster tables?",
    "opt1": "Yes",
    "opt2": "No",
    "correctAns": "No",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "We need to create primary index explicitly.",
    "opt1": "Yes",
    "opt2": "No",
    "correctAns": "No",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Single record buffering should be used when",
    "opt1": "It should be used for large tables when there are few records accesses",
    "opt2": "It should be used in large table that have frequent access to records",
    "opt3": "It should be used for those tables where some of the fields of the table are needed",
    "opt4": "All of the above",
    "correctAns": "It should be used for large tables when there are few records accesses",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Pre-requisite for creating foreign key relationship is?",
    "opt1": "The domain of foreign key and primary key of the check table should be different.",
    "opt2": "The foreign key field and primary key of check table should the same domain",
    "opt3": "A value table to the domain must be assigned",
    "correctAns": "The foreign key field and primary key of check table should the same domain",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whenever we create and activate the table below index will get automatically created",
    "opt1": "Secondary index",
    "opt2": "Primary index",
    "opt3": "Unique index",
    "opt4": "None of the above",
    "correctAns": "Primary index",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "When we create the table, text table will automatically get created",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "correctAns": "False",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "We can create table maintenance with below types of screens.",
    "opt1": "Overview screen",
    "opt2": "Single screen",
    "opt3": "None of the above",
    "correctAns": ["Overview screen", "Single screen"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Among the below which is not the valid delivery class?",
    "opt1": "A - application table (master & transaction data)",
    "opt2": "C – customizing table",
    "opt3": "T – temporary storage data",
    "opt4": "S – system table",
    "correctAns": "T – temporary storage data",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Transaction code for maintaining table/view (through TMG) is.",
    "opt1": "Sm30",
    "opt2": "Sm13",
    "opt3": "Se30",
    "opt4": "Sm35",
    "correctAns": "Sm30",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "We have an option for events in table maintenance generator.",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "correctAns": "True",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can we create change document history (CDHDR / CDPOS entries) for custom tables?",
    "opt1": "Yes",
    "opt2": "No",
    "correctAns": "Yes",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the check tables and value tables?",
    "opt1": "Check table will be at field level checking.",
    "opt2": "Value table will be at domain level checking.",
    "opt3": "Value table will be at field level checking.",
    "opt4": "Check table will be at domain level checking.",
    "correctAns": [
      "Check table will be at field level checking.",
      "Value table will be at domain level checking."
    ],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is better to buffer a table when",
    "opt1": "When a table is read infrequently",
    "opt2": "When a table is linked to check tables",
    "opt3": "When a table is read frequently, and the data seldom changes",
    "opt4": "When a single record is to be picked up",
    "correctAns": "When a table is read frequently, and the data seldom changes",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Full Buffering would be appropriate for",
    "opt1": "Transaction Tables",
    "opt2": "Small Static tables",
    "opt3": "Internal Tables",
    "opt4": "Tables with generic Keys",
    "correctAns": "Small Static tables",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the Cardinality for the Node created for storing the Table?",
    "opt1": "1:1",
    "opt2": "0:1",
    "opt3": "n:n",
    "opt4": "0:n",
    "correctAns": "1:1",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Custom table names must begin with a Z and are restricted to 16 characters. Is this a true or a false statement?",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False (It can start with Y also)",
    "correctAns": "False (It can start with Y also)",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "The table that is referenced by the foreign key (in our example, YCUSTOMERS) is called the check table (table having primary key). State whether the statement is true or false.",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "correctAns": "True",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "The check table is also known as:",
    "opt1": "Dependent table",
    "opt2": "Parent table",
    "opt3": "Child table",
    "opt4": "Referenced table",
    "opt5": "primary key table",
    "correctAns": "Parent table",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Versions of an object that can exist in the ABAP dictionary?",
    "opt1": "Modifiable",
    "opt2": "Active",
    "correctAns": ["Modifiable", "Active"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Multiple inheritance can be achieved in ABAP?",
    "opt1": "True (through interface)",
    "opt2": "False",
    "correctAns": "True (through interface)",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is mandatory for the creation of table maintenance generator?",
    "opt1": "Function group",
    "correctAns": "Function group",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Buffering is recommended for tables with data typically that does change or gets updated frequently",
    "opt1": "False",
    "opt2": "True",
    "correctAns": "False",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Material master data and its description is stored in the table.",
    "opt1": "MARA-MARKT",
    "opt2": "SPFLI",
    "opt3": "SFLIGHT",
    "correctAns": "MARA-MARKT",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "You define a formal parameter to a subroutine that accepts only internal table of type standard and type sorted as actual parameters. Which of the following generic ABAP data types must you use?",
    "opt1": "Hashed table",
    "opt2": "Standard table",
    "opt3": "Index table",
    "opt4": "Sorted table",
    "correctAns": "Standard table",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Max Number of Primary Index in Transparent table?",
    "opt1": "1",
    "opt2": "4",
    "opt3": "6",
    "correctAns": "1",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Max Number of Secondary Index in Transparent table?",
    "opt1": "1",
    "opt2": "4",
    "opt3": "6",
    "correctAns": "6",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are ways in which Standard Tables can be enhanced?",
    "opt1": "Custom include",
    "opt2": "Direct field addition",
    "opt3": "Append structure",
    "correctAns": ["Custom include", "Append structure"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which table type would be most appropriate for accessing table rows using an index?",
    "opt1": "Hashed table",
    "opt2": "Standard table",
    "opt3": "Sorted table",
    "opt4": "None of these may be accessed using an index.",
    "correctAns": "Hashed table",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "When creating a transparent table in the ABAP Dictionary, which step automatically creates the table in the underlying database?",
    "opt1": "Adding technical settings to the table",
    "opt2": "Checking the table syntax",
    "opt3": "Saving the table",
    "opt4": "Activating the table",
    "correctAns": "Activating the table",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "A dictionary table is made available for use within an ABAP program via the TABLES statement.",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "correctAns": "True",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "Name the type of ABAP Dictionary table that has these characteristics: Same number of fields as the database table, Same name as database table and Maps 1:1 to database table",
    "opt1": "Pooled",
    "opt2": "Cluster",
    "opt3": "Transparent",
    "opt4": "View",
    "correctAns": "Transparent",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a table does not have MANDT as part of the primary key, it is.",
    "opt1": "A structure",
    "opt2": "Invalid",
    "opt3": "Client-independent",
    "opt4": "Not mandatory",
    "correctAns": "Client-independent",
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many types of tables exist in data dictionary? (Multiple Answer)",
    "opt1": "Transparent tables",
    "opt2": "Internal Table",
    "opt3": "Pool tables",
    "opt4": "Hash Table",
    "opt5": "Cluster tables",
    "opt6": "Master Data Table",
    "correctAns": ["Transparent tables", "Pool tables", "Cluster tables"],
    "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
    "proposedAns": ""
  }
]